https://www.myssp.com/privacy-policy

Skip to Content
Privacy Policy
Home
Privacy Policy
SSP | Stainless Steel Products – Fittings, Valves, Fabrication {Hydraulic & Instrumentation Tube, Hose & Pipe Fittings} is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the SSP | Stainless Steel Products – Fittings, Valves, Fabrication {Hydraulic & Instrumentation Tube, Hose & Pipe Fittings} Web site and governs data collection and usage. By using the SSP | Stainless Steel Products – Fittings, Valves, Fabrication {Hydraulic & Instrumentation Tube, Hose & Pipe Fittings} website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
SSP | Stainless Steel Products – Fittings, Valves, Fabrication {Hydraulic & Instrumentation Tube, Hose & Pipe Fittings} collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. SSP | Stainless Steel Products – Fittings, Valves, Fabrication {Hydraulic & Instrumentation Tube, Hose & Pipe Fittings} also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.
There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by SSP | Stainless Steel Products – Fittings, Valves, Fabrication {Hydraulic & Instrumentation Tube, Hose & Pipe Fittings}. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by SSP | Stainless Steel Products – Fittings, Valves, Fabrication {Hydraulic & Instrumentation Tube, Hose & Pipe Fittings} for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the SSP | Stainless Steel Products – Fittings, Valves, Fabrication {Hydraulic & Instrumentation Tube, Hose & Pipe Fittings} Web site.
Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through SSP | Stainless Steel Products – Fittings, Valves, Fabrication {Hydraulic & Instrumentation Tube, Hose & Pipe Fittings} public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: SSP | Stainless Steel Products – Fittings, Valves, Fabrication {Hydraulic & Instrumentation Tube, Hose & Pipe Fittings} does not read any of your private online communications.
SSP | Stainless Steel Products – Fittings, Valves, Fabrication {Hydraulic & Instrumentation Tube, Hose & Pipe Fittings} encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from SSP | Stainless Steel Products – Fittings, Valves, Fabrication {Hydraulic & Instrumentation Tube, Hose & Pipe Fittings} so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. SSP | Stainless Steel Products – Fittings, Valves, Fabrication {Hydraulic & Instrumentation Tube, Hose & Pipe Fittings} is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the SSP | Stainless Steel Products – Fittings, Valves, Fabrication {Hydraulic & Instrumentation Tube, Hose & Pipe Fittings} and SSP | Stainless Steel Products – Fittings, Valves, Fabrication {Hydraulic & Instrumentation Tube, Hose & Pipe Fittings} family of Web sites.
Use of your Personal Information
SSP | Stainless Steel Products – Fittings, Valves, Fabrication {Hydraulic & Instrumentation Tube, Hose & Pipe Fittings} collects and uses your personal information to operate the SSP | Stainless Steel Products – Fittings, Valves, Fabrication {Hydraulic & Instrumentation Tube, Hose & Pipe Fittings} Web site and deliver the services you have requested. SSP | Stainless Steel Products – Fittings, Valves, Fabrication {Hydraulic & Instrumentation Tube, Hose & Pipe Fittings} also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from SSP | Stainless Steel Products – Fittings, Valves, Fabrication {Hydraulic & Instrumentation Tube, Hose & Pipe Fittings} and its affiliates. SSP | Stainless Steel Products – Fittings, Valves, Fabrication {Hydraulic & Instrumentation Tube, Hose & Pipe Fittings} may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.
SSP | Stainless Steel Products – Fittings, Valves, Fabrication {Hydraulic & Instrumentation Tube, Hose & Pipe Fittings} does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. SSP | Stainless Steel Products – Fittings, Valves, Fabrication {Hydraulic & Instrumentation Tube, Hose & Pipe Fittings} may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, SSP | Stainless Steel Products – Fittings, Valves, Fabrication {Hydraulic & Instrumentation Tube, Hose & Pipe Fittings} may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to SSP | Stainless Steel Products – Fittings, Valves, Fabrication {Hydraulic & Instrumentation Tube, Hose & Pipe Fittings}, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
SSP | Stainless Steel Products – Fittings, Valves, Fabrication {Hydraulic & Instrumentation Tube, Hose & Pipe Fittings} does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.
SSP | Stainless Steel Products – Fittings, Valves, Fabrication {Hydraulic & Instrumentation Tube, Hose & Pipe Fittings} keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within SSP | Stainless Steel Products – Fittings, Valves, Fabrication {Hydraulic & Instrumentation Tube, Hose & Pipe Fittings}, in order to determine what SSP | Stainless Steel Products – Fittings, Valves, Fabrication {Hydraulic & Instrumentation Tube, Hose & Pipe Fittings} services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within SSP | Stainless Steel Products – Fittings, Valves, Fabrication {Hydraulic & Instrumentation Tube, Hose & Pipe Fittings} to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
SSP | Stainless Steel Products – Fittings, Valves, Fabrication {Hydraulic & Instrumentation Tube, Hose & Pipe Fittings} Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on SSP | Stainless Steel Products – Fittings, Valves, Fabrication {Hydraulic & Instrumentation Tube, Hose & Pipe Fittings} or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of SSP | Stainless Steel Products – Fittings, Valves, Fabrication {Hydraulic & Instrumentation Tube, Hose & Pipe Fittings}; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of SSP | Stainless Steel Products – Fittings, Valves, Fabrication {Hydraulic & Instrumentation Tube, Hose & Pipe Fittings}, or the public.
Use of Cookies
The SSP | Stainless Steel Products – Fittings, Valves, Fabrication {Hydraulic & Instrumentation Tube, Hose & Pipe Fittings} Web site use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize SSP | Stainless Steel Products – Fittings, Valves, Fabrication {Hydraulic & Instrumentation Tube, Hose & Pipe Fittings} pages, or register with SSP | Stainless Steel Products – Fittings, Valves, Fabrication {Hydraulic & Instrumentation Tube, Hose & Pipe Fittings} site or services, a cookie helps SSP | Stainless Steel Products – Fittings, Valves, Fabrication {Hydraulic & Instrumentation Tube, Hose & Pipe Fittings} to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same SSP | Stainless Steel Products – Fittings, Valves, Fabrication {Hydraulic & Instrumentation Tube, Hose & Pipe Fittings} Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the SSP | Stainless Steel Products – Fittings, Valves, Fabrication {Hydraulic & Instrumentation Tube, Hose & Pipe Fittings} features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the SSP | Stainless Steel Products – Fittings, Valves, Fabrication {Hydraulic & Instrumentation Tube, Hose & Pipe Fittings} services or Web sites you visit.
Security of your Personal Information
SSP | Stainless Steel Products – Fittings, Valves, Fabrication {Hydraulic & Instrumentation Tube, Hose & Pipe Fittings} secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. SSP | Stainless Steel Products – Fittings, Valves, Fabrication {Hydraulic & Instrumentation Tube, Hose & Pipe Fittings} secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
Changes to this Statement
SSP | Stainless Steel Products – Fittings, Valves, Fabrication {Hydraulic & Instrumentation Tube, Hose & Pipe Fittings} will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. SSP | Stainless Steel Products – Fittings, Valves, Fabrication {Hydraulic & Instrumentation Tube, Hose & Pipe Fittings} encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how SSP | Stainless Steel Products – Fittings, Valves, Fabrication {Hydraulic & Instrumentation Tube, Hose & Pipe Fittings} is protecting your information.
Contact Information
SSP | Stainless Steel Products – Fittings, Valves, Fabrication {Hydraulic & Instrumentation Tube, Hose & Pipe Fittings} welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that SSP | Stainless Steel Products – Fittings, Valves, Fabrication {Hydraulic & Instrumentation Tube, Hose & Pipe Fittings} has not adhered to this Statement, please contact SSP | Stainless Steel Products – Fittings, Valves, Fabrication {Hydraulic & Instrumentation Tube, Hose & Pipe Fittings} at webmaster@wrsg.com. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
How To Avoid CommonInstrumentation Tube Fitting Mistakes
Avoid costly mistakes in selection and installation
Minimize risk & optimize performance
Ensure the longevity & reliability of your system
Yes, I Want The Free Guide!
No Thanks
Contact Us
Have a Question?Contact Us Now
